[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question" : "Jazz and Civic are models from which brand??",
        "options": [
            "Samsung",
            "Toyota",
            "Honda",
            "Motorola"
        ],
        "answer": "Honda"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question" : "Which animal is said to never forget??",
        "options": [
            "Giraffe",
            "Chimpanzee",
            "Cobra",
            "Elephant"
        ],
        "answer": "Elephant"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question" : "Which adjective is used to describe countries like Norway, Sweden, Denmark, Finland and Iceland?",
        "options": [
            "Scandinavian",
            "Nordic",
            "Siberian",
            "Arctic"
        ],
        "answer": "Nordic"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question" : "General Franco was dictator of which country from 1939 to 1975?",
        "options": [
            "France",
            "Spain",
            "Portugal",
            "Italy"
        ],
        "answer": "Spain"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question" : "What does a cartophilist collect?",
        "options": [
            "Cigarette cards",
            "maps",
            "carts",
            "travel photos"
        ],
        "answer": "Cigarette cards"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question" : "Wolfgang is the first name of which famous composer?",
        "options": [
            "Beethoven",
            "Mozart",
            "Berlioz",
            "Puccini"
        ],
        "answer": "Mozart"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question" : "What is a corncrake?",
        "options": [
            "cake",
            "plant",
            "bird",
            "farming method"
        ],
        "answer": "bird"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question" : "Katniss Everdeen is a character from which series of novels that have been made into movies?",
        "options": [
            "The Maze Runner",
            "Harry Potter",
            "The Handmaid's Tale",
            "The Hunger Games"
        ],
        "answer": "The Hunger Games"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question" : "Only one chess piece can only move diagonally - which is it??",
        "options": [
            "Pawn",
            "Knight",
            "Bishop",
            "Rook"
        ],
        "answer": "Bishop"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question" : "KLM is an airline based in which country?",
        "options": [
            "Netherlands",
            "The United States of America",
            "Kuwait",
            "South Korea"
        ],
        "answer": "Netherlands"
    }
]